hey, buddy
you don't waste time, do you?
I try not to
Hey, you need help?
sure
would you like to tell us what the hell that was all about ?
I don't like goodd-byes
Kind of the point of a good-bye party, John
Went to a certain amount of trouble, you know ?
could've at least stayed a few minutes, huh ?
Eaten some of the food we so feverishly prepared ?
I apologise , Harry
But why are you moving so quickly?
You only resigned a couple of days ago.
you got the history chair at Stanford.
I wish.
Well, taquitos, chicken wings, Roastie-Toasties and beer.
If we'd had more time, we'd have done something a little more grandiose.
Candlelight dinner at McDonald's. Strippers.
Taquitos are fine.